

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/</id>
  <title>Pwn3d</title>
  <subtitle>Young cybersecurity enthusiast passionate about offensive security and malware analysis. Always seeking new attack vectors and challenges.</subtitle>
  <updated>2025-08-09T22:21:17+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    <uri>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/</uri>
  </author>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/feed.xml"/>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"
    href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/"/>
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator>
  <rights> © 2025 x-pwn3d </rights>
  <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon>
  <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo>


  
  <entry>
    <title>Capture - TryHackMe</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Capture/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Capture - TryHackMe" />
    <published>2025-08-09T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-08-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Capture/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Capture/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="TryHackMe" />
    
  

  <summary>Can you bypass the login form?  This machine, named Capture!, is part of TryHackMe and rated as an easy challenge. It offers a great opportunity to practice fundamental web enumeration and brute force techniques while dealing with common protections like captchas. Throughout this challenge, we’ll explore how to identify valid usernames, automate captcha solving, and brute force passwords to gai...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>TakeOver - TryHackMe</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/TakeOver/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TakeOver - TryHackMe" />
    <published>2025-06-22T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-06-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/TakeOver/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/TakeOver/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="TryHackMe" />
    
  

  <summary>This machine is part of TryHackMe and is rated as an easy-level Linux challenge. While its rating suggests a straightforward box, TakeOver delivers a great hands-on introduction to SSL certificate inspection, subdomain enumeration, and host header exploitation. We’ll combine classical recon techniques with a bit of creativity to find hidden infrastructure and extract the final flag.  Let’s dive...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>MD2PDF - TryHackMe</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/MD2PDF/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MD2PDF - TryHackMe" />
    <published>2025-06-09T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-06-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/MD2PDF/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/MD2PDF/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="TryHackMe" />
    
  

  <summary>This machine is part of TryHackMe and is rated as an easy-level Linux challenge. Despite its rating, it offers a solid introduction to web enumeration, access control bypass, and creative client-side exploitation. Throughout the box, we’ll identify restricted resources, find clever ways to access them using browser-side vectors like iframes, and ultimately retrieve the flag hidden behind intern...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Dog - Hack The Box</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Dog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dog - Hack The Box" />
    <published>2025-05-03T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-05-03T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Dog/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Dog/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Hack The Box" />
    
  

  <summary>Dog is an easy-level Linux machine on Hack The Box (HTB) that provides a great introduction to source code leakage, CMS exploitation, and basic privilege escalation techniques. In this walkthrough, we’ll move from passive enumeration of public files like .git, to identifying hardcoded credentials, exploiting a known vulnerability in Backdrop CMS for Remote Code Execution (RCE), and finally leve...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Support - Hack The Box</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Support/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Support - Hack The Box" />
    <published>2025-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-05-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Support/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Support/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Hack The Box" />
    
  

  <summary>Support is an easy-level Windows machine on Hack The Box (HTB) that offers a great introduction to Active Directory exploitation, focusing on machine account manipulation, delegation abuse, and Kerberos ticket attacks. In this walkthrough, we’ll go from basic enumeration all the way to full DOMAIN ADMIN access by taking advantage of a subtle privilege misconfiguration and some clever ticket for...</summary>

  </entry>

</feed>


