

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/</id>
  <title>Pwn3d</title>
  <subtitle>Young cybersecurity enthusiast passionate about offensive security and malware analysis. Always seeking new attack vectors and challenges.</subtitle>
  <updated>2025-09-30T14:08:50+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    <uri>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/</uri>
  </author>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/feed.xml"/>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"
    href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/"/>
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator>
  <rights> © 2025 x-pwn3d </rights>
  <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon>
  <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo>


  
  <entry>
    <title>Hack The Box Academy — Penetration Tester Job Role Path (Cheat-Sheet)</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/PenetrationTester/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hack The Box Academy — Penetration Tester Job Role Path (Cheat-Sheet)" />
    <published>2025-09-30T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-09-30T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/PenetrationTester/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/PenetrationTester/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="Hack The Box" />
    
    <category term="Job Role Path" />
    
  

  <summary>Hack The Box Academy – Penetration Tester Job Role Path  Overview  Between May and September 2025, I completed the Hack The Box Academy Penetration Tester Job Role Path in just under five months. This structured learning path is designed to build both foundational and intermediate penetration testing skills, aligned with the real-world workflow of a professional pentester.  The path includes 28...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Soupedecode 01 - TryHackMe</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Soupedecode/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Soupedecode 01 - TryHackMe" />
    <published>2025-08-15T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-08-15T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Soupedecode/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Soupedecode/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="TryHackMe" />
    
    <category term="CTF" />
    
  

  <summary>This machine, named Soupedecode, is an intense and highly engaging Windows challenge. It revolves around compromising a domain controller by leveraging multiple Active Directory attack vectors. Throughout the engagement, we will enumerate SMB shares, perform password spraying against Kerberos authentication, and utilize Pass-the-Hash techniques to escalate privileges. This challenge offers a re...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>Capture - TryHackMe</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Capture/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Capture - TryHackMe" />
    <published>2025-08-09T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-08-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Capture/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/Capture/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="TryHackMe" />
    
    <category term="CTF" />
    
  

  <summary>Can you bypass the login form?  This machine, named Capture!, is part of TryHackMe and rated as an easy challenge. It offers a great opportunity to practice fundamental web enumeration and brute force techniques while dealing with common protections like captchas. Throughout this challenge, we’ll explore how to identify valid usernames, automate captcha solving, and brute force passwords to gai...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>TakeOver - TryHackMe</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/TakeOver/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TakeOver - TryHackMe" />
    <published>2025-06-22T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-06-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/TakeOver/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/TakeOver/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="TryHackMe" />
    
    <category term="CTF" />
    
  

  <summary>This machine is part of TryHackMe and is rated as an easy-level Linux challenge. While its rating suggests a straightforward box, TakeOver delivers a great hands-on introduction to SSL certificate inspection, subdomain enumeration, and host header exploitation. We’ll combine classical recon techniques with a bit of creativity to find hidden infrastructure and extract the final flag.  Let’s dive...</summary>

  </entry>

  
  <entry>
    <title>MD2PDF - TryHackMe</title>
    <link href="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/MD2PDF/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MD2PDF - TryHackMe" />
    <published>2025-06-09T00:00:00+02:00</published>
  
    <updated>2025-06-09T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
  
    <id>https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/MD2PDF/</id>
    <content type="text/html" src="https://x-pwn3d.github.io/posts/MD2PDF/" />
    <author>
      <name>x-pwn3d</name>
    </author>

  
    
    <category term="TryHackMe" />
    
    <category term="CTF" />
    
  

  <summary>This machine is part of TryHackMe and is rated as an easy-level Linux challenge. Despite its rating, it offers a solid introduction to web enumeration, access control bypass, and creative client-side exploitation. Throughout the box, we’ll identify restricted resources, find clever ways to access them using browser-side vectors like iframes, and ultimately retrieve the flag hidden behind intern...</summary>

  </entry>

</feed>


